Guide to the Thomas Cover Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Talks, Series 3
  - "Comments on Speech and Information" - Johns Hopkins Speech Workshop, 1995 Aug 7 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - "Responses on Speech" - Johns Hopkins Speech Workshop, 1995 Aug 7 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Information Efficiency in Investment - IEEE ISIT Whistler, 1995 Sept 18 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Ordentlich: Side Information - UCSC, 1995 Oct 11 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Pinkser talk: Gaussian Feedback Cap… - IEEE IT Whistler, 1995 Sept 19 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - ISL Overview, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Welcoming Remarks - ISL Orientation, 1995 Sept 25 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - "Multiple Access and Broadcast Comm." - EE370 Talk, 1995 Nov 30 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - "The Role of Feedback in Communication" - K.T. Li Symposium, Taiwan, 1995 Nov 8 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Max-Min Optimal Investing - Santa Cruz, Calif, 1996 May 4-5 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Kullback Memorial Research Conf. - Washington, DC, 1996 May24-25 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - "Max-Min Optimal Investing" - CIFER, New York, 1996 March (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - ISL Summary - Admittee's Day, 1996 March 22 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - "Robust Data Compression" - JSEP Talk, 1996 Aug (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Colt - Italy, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - "Minimax Regret Universal Portfolios" - IMS'96 Chicago, IL, 1996 Aug (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - "Efficiency of Information in Investment" - E. Erkip Orals Talk, 1996 July (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - "Universal Investment & Universal Data Compression" - E. Ordentlich Oral Exam, 1996 July (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Information Theory Workshop - Haifa, Israel, 1996 June 9-13 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - "Universal Data Compression & Port. Sel - FOCS96 Burlington, VT, 1996 Oct 14-16 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - "Universal data comp. & port. Selection" - Pasadena Tutorial, 1996 Nov (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Equivalence of Market Gain & Minimax Regret Universal Portfolios" - ISIT, Ulm, Germany, 1997 June (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Relationship of data comp. & investment" - DCC, Snowbird, Utah, 1997 March (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Universal Data Compression & Invest. - Stanford EE370 Seminar, 1997 Nov 13 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - IEEE ISIT - Ulm, Germany, 1997 June 29-July4 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Entropy Day, Israeli Academy of Science, 1998 Dec 16 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - MURI talk, 2000 Aug 16 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 52-card channel (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - "Shannen Theory and Investment" - Stanford CSLI Workshop, 1998 May 30 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - IEEE IT Universal portfolios with short selling and margin. T. Cover/E.Ordentlich, Aug.1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - ISIT Symposium, Boston: Universal portfolios w/short & margin, Aug.1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University EE370 "Universal Port. w/Short & Margin", 1998 Oct.15 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - University of Maryland. Data compression & investment, 1997 Oct.24 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - IEEE IT, San Diego. "Some unresolved problems in IT", 1998 Feb.8-11 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Shannon Day, Murray Hill. "Shannon theory and investment", 1998 May 18 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - CS seminar. "Comments on the value of information", 1998 Mar. 9 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - DARPA video conference workshop. Comments on info theory, 1999 Dec.2 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Isaac Newton Institute, Cambridge, UK., 1999 summer (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Info theory and networking workshop, Metsovo, Greece (Greece talk + handouts), 1999 June 27-July 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - IEEE Comm. Theory workshop, Santa Cruz. Poker hands & channels w/ known state, 1999 May 26 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - ISL Affiliates meeting. "Communication, data compression …", 1999 Apr.29 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - University of Arizona. Kelly Gambling, Universal data compr…, 1999 April 21 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Statistics Dept. Unresolved problems, 1999 Feb.23 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bergerfest, 2000 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - IT Workshop, Hungary. Info theory, data …, 2000 July (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NIPS tutorial, Denver. "Information theory", 2000 Nov.27 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - IT 2000. T.Cover panel on future of IT, 2000 June (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - ISIT Sorrento, Italy. Trip file, 2000 June 25-30 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Hungary travel receipts and arrangements, 2000 July (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Balatonlelle [Hungary] :Info theory in Math, 2000 July 4-7 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - IT 2000 talks (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - LIDS/MIT talk: Data compression & investment, 2000 March (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Forney Fest talk: Bell's inequality, 2000 March 3 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - AAAS meeting, 2000 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - AAAS talk: Universal data compression & universal portfolios, 2000 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - AI Conference, Seattle. Information theory tutorial, 2001 Aug.12 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Stat seminar: Odd angles in sports and gambling, 2001 Apr.17 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - AAAS meeting, San Francisco. Odd angles in sports, 2001 Feb.16 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - ISIT, Washington DC. Duality/channel capacity/rate …, 2001 June (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - ISL Affiliates program. Eight problems with one answer, 2001 April 6 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Stanford SNRC. Network information flow, 2001 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Barclay's, San Francisco. Universal data compression, 2001 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Stanford SNRC. Network information flow, 2001 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - MSRI, Berkeley. Rate/distortion tradeoff …, 2002 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - MSRI/MURI, Harvard. Role/side info/communication, 2002 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - SNRC Retreat/Costanoa. Network information flow, 2001 Nov. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Shannon Symposium, San Diego. Role of state information, 2001 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - McEliece workshop, Cal Tech. "Comments on synchronization", 2002 May 24-25 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - MURI talk, Harvard, 2002 Feb.26 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - MURI site visit, 2002 Feb.13 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Xerox Parc. Odd angles in sports and gambling., 2002 March (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - India IT workshop, Bangalore, 2002 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - IEEE workshop on Information theory, Bangalore. Concavity of second law, 2002 Oct.21 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Communication theory workshop, Sanibel., 2002 May 17-22 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - McEliece workshop, Cal Tech., 2002 May 24-25 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Honolulu Stat Conference. Oscillations/probability/winning, 2002 June (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - ISIT Lausanne, Switzerland. Concavity in time/conditional entropy, 2002 July (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - NSF Workshop, Chicago., 2003 Oct.17 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - AAAS induction, Boston, 2003 Oct.11 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Allerton Conference, Urbana-Champaign, 2003 Oct.1 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - IEE Conference, Washington. Info. Capacity & stock market, 2003 Sept. 19 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - ISIT Yokohama., 2003 June 26-July 5 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - BAD Day, Berkeley, Ca., 2004 Feb.13 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - NAE Keck Conference, Irvine, Calif., 2003 Nov.16 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - BAMA talk. Idiosyncracies in sports and gambling., 2003 Nov.5 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - MSRI Conference, 2004 June (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Allerton BOG meeting, 2003 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - IT, Orlando FL Information beyond Shannon, 2005 Oct.27-28 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - ISIT 2005, Adelaide, 2005 Sept. 4-9 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - ISIT Adelaide. Statistic for evaluating side info., 2005 Sept. (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - IT workshop, Orlando, FL, 2005 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - IEEE ISIT. Adelaide, Aust., 2005 Sept. 4-9 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - MaxEnt 2005, San Jose, 2005 Aug.7-12 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - MaxEnt 2005, San Jose State Univ. Burg intro, 2005 Aug.8 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Canadian Workshop on Information Theory. Call for papers, 2005, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - ISITA & JWCCC, Parma & Florence, Italy, 2004 Oct.10-17 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Stanford - SNRC Network information flow, 2005 Feb.17 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - IT Workshop, San Antonio TX "didn't go", 2004 Oct.24-29 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Parma, Italy. Info loss in the joints, 2004 Oct.10 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - John Burg talk: John Burg and maximum entropy, 2005 Aug.8 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Stanford U. Intro to Kailath lecture, 2005 9 June (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NAE CATS, Washington DC., 2004 Sept.29-30 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - IEEE ISIT, Chicago., 2004 June 26-July 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - IEEE ISIT, Chicago., 2004 June (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bill & Omeara wedding, 2006 Oct.13-14 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Kailath Lecture, Stanford, 2006 July 6-7 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - ITA Workshop, San Diego, 2006 Feb.6-10 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - ITW, Punta del Este, Uruguay, 2006 March 14-17 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Cioffi/Marconi Award, 2006 Oct.12 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Fuzzy Day talk, New York, 2006 June (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - IEEE ISIT, Seattle, WA, 2006 July 9-14 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - OTA Asset Management, New York, 2006 June 18-20 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - USCD, La Jolla. Info Theory & Applications, 2006 Feb.6-20 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Universal portfolios, 2006 June (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - International Joint Conference on Neural Networks, Orlando FL, 2007 Aug.12-17 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ISIT, Nice, France, 2007 June 24-29 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - NSF panel, Arlington VA, 2007 May 7-8 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - ITA Workshop, UC San Diego, 2007 Jan.28-Feb.1 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Budapest, Hungary talk: Information and communication, 2008 Aug.23-29 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - IEEE ISIT,Toronto, 2008 July 6-11 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Information beyond Shannon workshop, Venice "not going", 2008 Dec.29-30 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - University of Texas, Austin TX, 2008 Oct.31 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - JWCC 2008, Napa, Calif., 2008 Oct.26-28 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Purdue CS Dept., West Lafayette, IN talk, 2008 Oct.19-21 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - USC talk, Los Angeles, 2008 Oct.16 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - EE faculty/TC research talk, 2008 Oct.13 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Stanford talk, 2008 Oct.6 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - ITA Workshop, UC San Diego, 2008 Jan.28-Feb.1 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - ITA 2009, San Diego, 2009 Feb.8-9 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Cornell School of Information theory talk, 2009 June 19-22 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - ISL retreat, Half Moon Bay, CA, 2010 Oct.8-9 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Trip report, ITA San Diego: Bergerfest, Blackwell Mem., 2011 Feb.4-11 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Blackwell session, T. Cover, organizer, 2011 Feb.10 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Shannon Memorial Lecture: Kolmogorov's contributions to information theory, 1989, 2011 Sept.19 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - K.T. Li/Taiwan/Embassy, 2009 Nov. (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Isaac Newton Institute for Mathematical Sciences, 2009 Jan. (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Information theory and the stock market, [none] (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Conferences attended (as of June 1992) (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Administrative files, Series 4
  - EE 278, Autumn 99 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - EE 278, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - EE 278 - Gray's & AEG's Notes, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Garud Papers, 2000 May (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mung Chiang and TC Paper, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Evolution of Complexity, 1996 May 30 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - I.T. Wash D.C. Papers, 2000 Sept 25 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bell's Inequality, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bell Storage, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Projection of Simplex Assaf and TC, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Unlabeled Photo, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Lorenz, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Lorenz, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Concavity Second Law, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Concavity of H(xn, x0) Second Law, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Papers on Portfolio Theory, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Demoth Photo Slides, 1994 June 14 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Probability Qualifying Examination, 2002 Aug. 28 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Email, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Corresp., 1977, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Intro to Stochastic Processes Handouts/Exam, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - EE 376B, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bio, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Corresp., 1993-1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Photos, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Notes on Panel Discussion, 2000 June (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Information Theory, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Mountain View Analystics-Forward Management Joint Venture, 2002 Dec. 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Acceleration Univ., undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Various Notes (Entropy, Capacity, etc.), undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Codinf and Transmission over Source-Dependent Channels, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - E.P. Conjectures, 1982 Feb. 22 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Mark Lyon, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Quantum I.T., 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Zig-Zag Path to Understanding, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Is Quantum Mechanics Useful?, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Statistical Distane and the Geometry of Quatum States, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - The Fundamental Role of Chaos in Statistical Physics, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Gravitation, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Hypersensitivity to Perturbations in the Quatum baker's Map, 1993 July 26 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - The Relatioship Between PAC, the Statistical Physics Framework, the Bayesian Framework, and the VC Framework, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Does Gardening Decrease Entropy? A remark on the Definition of Entropy, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Papers by JLL, 1993 Sept. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Quatum Physics and Communication Engineering, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Breaking Intractability, 1994 Jan. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Entropy is Not a Physical Property of Microscopic Physical States, 1996 July 27 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - One Plus One is Not Two, 1996 Oct. 25 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - To Send dat, Physicists Resort to Quatum Voodoo, 1996 Oct. 25 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Quatum Conference, 1997 March 20-21 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Quatum Information and Computation: Theory and Practice, 1996 Nov.-Dec. (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Quatum Encoding, 1996 Nov.-Dec. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Quatum vs. Classical Information, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Information Measures, Effective Complexity, adn Total Information, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Quatum I.T., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - reversible Electronic Logic Using Switches, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - The Fundamental Physical Constants, 1997 Aug. (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Battle Recontres, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Physics and Austerity: Laws Without Law, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - To Send Data. Physicists Resort to Quatum Voodoo, 1996 Oct. 25 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Various Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Ziemba, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Teaching Evaluation Report, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Hal Stern, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Young-Han Kim, 2001-2004 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - YHK Univ Prediction, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - YHK, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - YHK, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - YHK Multiple Relays, 2001 October (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Relay YHK, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - YHK, 2003 Aug (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Lists, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Universal Portfolio with Transaction Costs, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Garud Identifiability, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - NSF Proposal, 2002 Dec 12 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - MURI, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - MURI Correspondence, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - NSF Proposal, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - MURI Carlos Stroud, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - JSEP Supported Papers, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - MURI Report, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Maps - MURI Rochester, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - MURI, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Muri Related Papers, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - DARPA Paul Kozenchak, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - NSF Folder, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Tom Cover B.O.G., 2001 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - I.T. BOG Mtg., 2002 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Rochester and Ithica/Cornell, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - MURI, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - San Diego Shannon Symposium, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - DIMACS, Rutgers University, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - MURI, 2001 Aug 27-31 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - MURI Baltimore Conference, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - BoG Meeting/CISS - Princeton, NJ, 2002 Feb 22 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - ISIT Symp, Switzerland, 2002 June (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - NSF, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - NSF ITMANET Proposal, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - SNRC, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - NRC Proposal, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - National Academy of Engineering Member Comments, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Elements of Info Theory Prelim Draft, 1989 Sept. 22 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - EIT Solutions, 2007 Aug. 23 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Network Info Theory Chapter 15 2nd Edition Revisions, 2003 May 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Elements of Info Theory Congrats, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Open Problems in Communication and Computation, 1977-1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Abstracts, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Abstacts, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - ISL Misc. Flyers, Info, Sheets..., 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Bio, 1996 July 13 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Backgammon, 1977, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Backgammon, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Newest Nbr. Draft, 1960, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Book Ch. 2 amd Ch. 3 Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Various Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Performance of the Nearest Neighbor Rule with Finite Sample Sets, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Professors, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Estimation by the Nearest Neighbor Rule, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Estimation by the Nearest Neighbor Rule Abstract, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Estimation by the Nearest Neighbor Rule Abstract Another Annotated, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Various Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Nearest Neighbor Classification, 1966 June 15-17 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Distibution for the Smallest Distance between Any Pair of kth Nearest Neighbor Random Points on a Line, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Nearest Neighbor Classification Annotated Copy, 1966 Feb. 20 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Various Notes, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Office Memorandum, 1965 May 14 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - The Nearest Neigbor Rule, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Nearest Neighbor Rule and Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - The Nearest Neighbor Decision Rule, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Notes (Estimation, Sample Size of One, Unequal Losses. etc.), 1964 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Note on Simple Classifier, 1964 July 21 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Nearest Neighbor Rule Conjectures, 1964 July 21 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Unequal Costs, 1964 Aug. 9 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Notes, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Sliding Cells to Equalize Number of Observations in Each Cell, 1964 Sept. 20 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Nearest Neighbor rule Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Monotaniaty in n, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Proof Notes, 1964 Jan. 6 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Conjecture Using k, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Conjecture by N.A., 1964 Oct. 15 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Systems Theory review Talk, 1965 July 6 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - An Asymptotic Analysis of the Nearest Neighbor Decision Rule, 1965 June 20 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Notes, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Theoretical and Experimental Investigations in Trainable Pattern-Classifying Systems, 1965 Sept. (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - NN Final Draft Review Correspondence, 1966 April 30 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - A Class of Non-Parametric Estimates of A Smooth Regression Function, 1966 Aug. 11 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - An Symptotic Analysis of the Nearest-Neighbor Decision Rule, 1966 May (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - About Transfer Functions with Approximately Constant Time-Delay, 1965 Dec. 27 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - The Condensed Nearest-Neighnor Rule, 1966 Oct. 28 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Permission to Reprint Article, 2009 Jan. (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Stats 50 Team Captian Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Single Quatum Interference, 1959 May 20 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Prestine Lecture Series on Science of Information Ad., 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Hawaii Talk, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Inforamtion Hurts, 2002 Oct. 16 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Quatum Inforamtion/Broadcast Channels/ Gaussian Channels, etc., 1990-2002 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Stanford University School of Engineering Annual Faculty Report, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Universal Portfolios with Short Selling and Margin, 1998 Aug. (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Email, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Email, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Fac Report, 2006-2008 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Papers Sent Out, 1974-1997 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Successive Refinement of Information, 1991 March (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Universal Portfolios with Side Information, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - The Cost of Achieving the Best Portfolio in Hindsight, 1997 Nov. 20 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Reviews, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Comments on E of I.T. from Masond Salehi, undated (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Telescona Proposals, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Excom Retreat, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - ITMANET, 2008-2011 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mathis, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Simplex Codes, 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Unlabeled Notes, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Random Matrices, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Charles Mathis, 2004 April (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - C. Mathis, 2005 Sep (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Three Recent Portfolio Papers, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Portfolio Papers, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Portfolio Papers, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Faculty Planner, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Weekly Appointbook, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Week At A Glance, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Week At A Glance academic Assignment, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Week At A Glance, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Weekly Appointbook, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Week At A Glance, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Week At A Glance, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Week At A Glance, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Week At A Glance, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Week At A Glance, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Week At A Glance, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Week At A Glance: Academic/Fiscal Planner, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Week At A Glance: Academic/Fiscal Planner, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Week At A Glance: Academic/Fiscal Planner, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Week At A Glance: Academic/Fiscal Planner, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Week At A Glance: Academic/Fiscal Planner, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Week At A Glance: Academic/Fiscal Planner, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Week At A Glance: Academic/Fiscal Planner, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Week At A Glance: Academic/Fiscal Planner, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Week At A Glance: Academic/Fiscal Planner, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Unlabeled Microcassettes, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Qual Qs, 1993-1997 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Conference Announcements, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Isaac Newton Institute Cambridge, UK, 1999 July 5-28 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Emails for Greece and Cambridge, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - CA State Lottery, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - MVA B.C., 2003 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - MVA CV's etc, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Ritchie Capital Management, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - MVA, 2003 May (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Photographs/Ephemera, Series 5
  - Elements of Information Theory Workshop (Coverfest), 2008 May 16 (Box 1)
    Photograph and poster from Coverfest 2008, held on the occasion of Tom Cover's 70th birthday.
- Website, 128 megabyte(s) (149 files in 5 directories)